Challenge complete.
>> Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben and Jerry's flavors, but
lower in calories and higher in protein.
This is Choco Lada Cheesecake Sundae.
Let me show you how to make it. We're
starting off with a chocolate cheesecake
base. So, we're using a chocolate
protein shake, some cream cheese,
sweetener, salt, cocoa powder, and some
[music] zantham gum. Then, we're mixing
that all up with an immersion blender,
capping it off, and throwing it in the
freezer for at least 16 hours. Then
you're going to take it out and run it
under hot water for about a minute and
then put it in your Ninja Creamy on the
light ice cream setting. There's a good
chance it'll come out pretty powdery.
That's completely fine as long as the
sides are slightly melted. It is ready
for mixins. So you can scrape down the
sides and then hollow a hole in the
center for your Oreos. We're using three
Oreo thins cream removed to remove some
of the calories. If you want to leave
the cream in, be my guest. Then we're
throwing it back in on the mix-in
setting. And after this, you're going to
have chocolate cheesecake Oreo ice cream
and it'll be delicious. But this Ben &
Jerry's flavor is a complex one. So,
we're just getting started. We're first
topping it with some fat-free ready whip
or any kind of whipped cream. And then
some sugar-free chocolate sauce and some
chopped up pieces of a salted chocolate
bar. I like this one from Horbulls
Torbull. It has a bit of added protein
and tastes great. And that's it, guys. I
need something harder. What should I
make next?